A la mierda eso.
I'm confiscating this.
Ma, lock it in the safe.
I'll come by later
for an examination.
What... what examination?
I'm sure you're the one
who shot at Gina last week.
But I need more than suspicion.
I want proof.
Walt,
you didn't give me an answer.
Dad,
becoming chairman,
that's what I wanted for a long time.
But I'm out.
I love Gina,
and I want to be with her.
Forget it.
Just forget it.
That woman can never
give you what's most important -
a legacy.
Enough Richard.
My sacrifice is enough.
You ruined my life.
You made Henry into a monster.
And now you want to steal
Walt's happiness?
No.
Leave him alone.
Let him be happy.
Why are you still here?
Thank you, Ma.
Dad.
Bro.